He's coming home to the war he never left.
Man Down is a thriller, drama, war film directed by Dito Montiel.
When a U.S.
Marine returns home from Afghanistan, he finds that the place he once called
home is no better than the battlefields he fought on overseas.
Accompanied by his best friend, he searches desperately for
the whereabouts of his estranged son and wife.
In their search, the two intercept a man carrying
vital information about his family.
Gabriel Drummer, played by Shia LaBeouf.
Devin Roberts, played by Jai Courtney.
Captain Peyton, played by Gary Oldman.
Natalie Drummer, played by Kate Mara.
Sergeant Miller, played by Tory Kittles.
Charles, played by Clifton Collins Jr..
Man Down is a 2015 American war thriller drama film
directed by Dito Montiel, written by Adam G.
Simon, and starring Shia LaBeouf, Jai Courtney, Gary
Oldman, Kate Mara, and Clifton Collins Jr.
The film follows a Marine who returns from Afghanistan to find his
hometown devastated, and his wife and son missing.
The film had its world premiere in the Horizon section at 72nd
Venice International Film Festival on September 6, 2015.
It was released on December 2, 2016, by Lionsgate
Premiere, to negative reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of dreams, delusion,
post-apocalyptic future, illusion, apocalypse.
The tone is emotional and intense.